<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live Learn Grow</title>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <link>http://localhost:8080</link>
    <description>Know Your Life</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
    <generator>Wintersmith - https://github.com/jnordberg/wintersmith</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Current interests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/articles/current/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/articles/current/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;rails&quot;&gt;Rails&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;opinionated - structured layout of development&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;backend - ruby, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;   rails new depot
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rails way of creating an APP&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Page flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data flow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;   cd depot
   rails generate scaffold Product \
            title:string description:text image_url:string price:decimal
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;- create products data
- migrate db
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;   rake db:migrate
   rails server
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;app/ config/ db/ Gemfile.lock log/ Rakefile test/ vendor/ bin/ config.ru
Gemfile lib/ public/ README.rdoc tmp/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/current/ruby-on-rails.png&quot; alt=&quot;Ruby On Rails&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>waterfall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/articles/waterfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2014 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/articles/waterfall/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;live-learn-grow&quot;&gt;Live Learn Grow&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A year ago I had an encounter with a waterfall and it changed my way of thinking …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thailand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/waterfall/bigisland.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waterfalls&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content and Code Usage Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/articles/content-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/articles/content-policy/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site will hopefully to continue to grow and have a lot of valuable content both in terms of articles and code.  I hope that everyone finds it to be a valuable tool.  That being said, there are a few ground rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any code that is included on this site is released under an &lt;a href=&quot;http://opensource.org/licenses/MIT&quot;&gt;MIT License&lt;/a&gt; unless another license is specified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some portions of code may be released under a license which does require attribution.  If you would like to use one of these pieces of software without attribution, please feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/about/#contact&quot;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;articles&quot;&gt;Articles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All articles on this site are licensed under a &lt;a rel=&quot;license&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/deed.en_US&quot;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License&lt;/a&gt;.  This means that all uses of this content must be attributed, and that no commercial uses are allowed.  If you wish to request a waiver of one or more of these terms, please &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/about/#contact&quot;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If at any point I reference one of my articles or publications which are published elsewhere, then that content remains under the license of the publisher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;additional-terms-and-policies&quot;&gt;Additional Terms and Policies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please take time to review the &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/terms-of-use/&quot;&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/privacy-policy/&quot;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; if you are interested in such things.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/articles/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/articles/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/articles/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/articles/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-license&quot;&gt;Use License&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Alex Davis’ (alex2006hw) web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Alex Davis’ (alex2006hw) web site;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Alex Davis (alex2006hw) at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;disclaimer&quot;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The materials on Alex Davis’ (alex2006hw) web site are provided “as is”. Alex Davis (alex2006hw) makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Alex Davis (alex2006hw) does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;limitations&quot;&gt;Limitations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Alex Davis (alex2006hw) or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Alex Davis’ (alex2006hw) Internet site, even if Alex Davis or (alex2006hw) authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;revisions-and-errata&quot;&gt;Revisions and Errata&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The materials appearing on Alex Davis’ web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Alex Davis does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Alex Davis may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Alex Davis does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex Davis has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Alex Davis of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;site-terms-of-use-modifications&quot;&gt;Site Terms of Use Modifications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex Davis may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;governing-law&quot;&gt;Governing Law&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any claim relating to Alex Davis’ web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>